Welcome!
- What benefits do you get from living at the top of Sweden?
- It's damn good to say.
- To say to ...
- Just everyone.
- A cloudy shit day.
So you get up here and you see sun.
- So some rainy days you take the elevator up and then it is sun again.
And the clouds are below you.
- You can stand down here on the ground, see the sunset go down.
Run in, the elevator up and see it again.
- That's how it is.
Is there any boat in the way?
No.
- Just that, you control in parallel here.
It is a constantly ongoing-
-mindfuck to see a living room-
-Oka around like this on the lake.
What a small boat you have!
Superpathetic!
Hahaha, now you have to be nice Mauri!
- Now we're going to eat ice cream.
Come and we eat ice cream.
- Oh, what are you doing?
You're so heaven ...
Hello?
You are so athletic!
- Send the ice cream.
- Oh, you're greedy.
- Yes, I want ice cream.
- You may not get any ice cream today.
- Then you must not be up here.
Well ...
What I am trying to say is that research shows that spending time with families and friends is the best thing you can do for your well -being.
And best is a joint dinner!
Come then we will practice sauce for real.
Follow here!
Then we spent the evening practicing sauce,--
-The also the doctrine of creating memorable dinners together.
And we could do nothing but pay tribute to Professor Lohmander,-
-Not just for his outstanding research, but also for the sauces he offers.
Invite your friends at dinner you with and serve them.
Lohmander's new barbeque!
Oh, damn!
Hello?
We are heading towards Vadstena in Östergötland.
There is a house that is built in a greenhouse.
It sounds really strange.
But it is such a sickly brilliant trick they have come up with.
This means that they have tropical heat at home with them year -round in Sweden.
And here it is a house in a greenhouse.
And now it's time to step in, my ladies and gentlemen.
I stand out.
It's cold.
Soon I step into as well as a tropical climate.
I step into a new world as well.
-It's almost the emotion-
-The bowl for you and you and for what you have done.
- Thanks!
And funny that you are here.
- Fun to be here.
- I have a long time in my life a dream.
I have always dreamed of literally being allowed to throw stones in glass houses.
Yes!
- I am so tired of redheads who will do a thing that they are red -haired.
- I'm so tired of all Iranians that are so successful.
- It's stone in glass houses!
Now it's stone in glass houses!
And now, my ladies and gentlemen, it's time for place number one.